<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<activity id="2087" moduleid="10198" modulename="label" contextid="73472">
  <label id="2087">
    <name>Connection to the LINCS Community Congratulations ...</name>
    <intro>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Connection to the LINCS Community&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Congratulations on completing &lt;em&gt;Engaging Adult Learners in Science&lt;/em&gt;! To continue your learning beyond the course and connect with other practitioners, we encourage you to join a LINCS Community Group! The &lt;a href="https://community.lincs.ed.gov/group/26" target="_blank"&gt;Science&lt;/a&gt; Group might be of particular interest based on your learning in this course. No matter which group(s) you choose, you will find discussions, resources, and live events to further develop your teaching practices and share your expertise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Continue Your Learning&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that you are familiar with the scientific practices and have explored ways to use them in your ABE/ASE classroom, consider taking other self-directed courses on LINCS &lt;a href="https://courses.lincs.ed.gov/" target="_blank"&gt;Courses&lt;/a&gt;. Courses under the &lt;a href="https://courses.lincs.ed.gov/course/index.php?categoryid=4" target="_blank"&gt;Science&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;heading focus on teaching science in adult basic education/adult secondary education (ABE/ASE) and English Language Acquisition (ELA) classes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Resources for Learners&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The LINCS &lt;a href="https://lincs.ed.gov/learner/" target="_blank"&gt;Learner Center&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;is a student-oriented site where adult learners can find resources for their own self-directed exploration and further learning. Check out the &lt;a href="https://lincs.ed.gov/learner/resources/science" target="_blank"&gt;Learn Science&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;page, among other goal-focused categories, and help learners make their own connections.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</intro>
    <introformat>1</introformat>
    <timemodified>1709951990</timemodified>
  </label>
</activity>